<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Documentation/Schemas/Amplitude.Unity.Localization.LocalizationDatatableElement.xsd">
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAISophons01Title">One of the Triumvirate</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAISophons01Description">Optymalization in every aspect of administration, exploration and exploitation was always favourite activity of this one.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAITerran01Title">Kinete the Academy Outcast</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAITerran01Description">There is no destiny , each one of us chooses own patch.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAIVampirilis01Title">Daro St Taiage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAIVampirilis01Description">Daro was known as "The Burning Brand' for her eager and relentless proselytization of minor peoples. Ever eager to bring additional souls into the fold and to free spirits from their physical prisons, the Fount upon her Ark never lacked for sacrifices. Her worldview changed one day, however, while rounding up recalcitrant Kalgeros who were hiding in an Endless temple. Touched by the presence of the Virtual Endless who called itself Taiage, Daro came face-to-face and soul-to-soul with one of her gods. The reality of this knowledge shocked and altered her profoundly. Still driven to serve a god, and yet sharing her Cloth with its presence, Daro now alternates between burning with faith and aggression and fearing what ultimate sacrifice her symbiotic saint may require of her. What is the recompense for sacrifice? What is the ultimate act of fidelity? It is one thing to act as if believing your god follows your every movement and thought; it is quite another thing to live that way.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAIVampirilis02Title">Varb St Zouieina</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSmartAIVampirilis02Description">If pressed to respond, Varb would indicate that his life began as a hydroponic farmer on a space station, a member of the Zolya Clan and a happy husband and father. When his system was taken by a Vodyani Ark ship and his people assimilated, Varb was one of the few whose spirits were deemed worthy to ascend to the gift of Vodyani citizenship. As mortal body was replaced by energy and Varb donned his Cloth and became a member of the Protectorate, little remained of the anger at his family's death and his own transformation. As a soldier of the Vodyani, Varb came to execute his duties professionally and faithfully. His attitude changed forever when he touched a ruin on a barren world, and came into unprepared contact with the living spirit of Zouieina. This Virtual, dying slowly in an underpowered site, was glad to find redemption and life as a Vodyani saint. While Varb felt a trace of amusement from Zouieina at the notion, the powers that his Cloth assumed from the spirit and the abilities that he gained were exceptional. Unhappily, Zouieina awoke in Varb memories of a lost family and of other ways that a people might choose to live. Torn but triumphant, overtly efficient but silently in turmoil, Varb is a hero who is not sure where he will stand when great Penance comes.</LocalizationPair>

</Datatable>
